Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Production Files, 146646
  - Subseries A: Mabou Mines stage productions, 146691
    - The Lost Ones University of Rhode Island April, 1977; 147252 (Box 7, Folder 295)
      see also oversize for poster
    - The Lost Ones / The B. Beaver Animation / Dressed Like an Egg Walker Art Center, 1977; 147251 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - The Lost Ones / The B. Beaver Animation North Shore Arts Center, Long Island, 1978; 147250 (Box 7, Folder 297)
      see also oversize
    - The Saint and the Football Players Philip Glass scores: "calling pieces", 1975; 147249 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - The Saint and the Football Players 28th Annual Connecticut College American Dance Festival; A Bunch of Experimental Theaters, 1975; 147248 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Cascando royalties, 1975; 147247 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Cascando The Public Theater, 1976; 147246 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Cascando box office, programs, 1976; 147245 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Cascando / The Lost Ones Florence; A Bunch of Experimental Theaters materials, 1976; 147244 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Dressed Like an Egg cues, 1979; 147243 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Sydney Opera House, 1980; 147242 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Dressed Like an Egg permission and royalty correspondence and contract, 1978; 147241 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema Lee Breuer speech, undated; 147240 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema press, 1980; 147239 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Vanishing Pictures photograph, undated; 147238 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Wrong Guys description, press, 1981; 147237 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Wrong Guys letters of agreement, 1981, 1987; 147236 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Wrong Guys press release, flyer, invitations, 1981; 147235 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Presents/Presence project description, undated; 147234 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Cold Harbor light hook-up, light cue sheets; Apple Corps Theatre March, 1987; 147233 (Box 8, Folder 314)
      see also oversize for light plots, gels
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235815
    - Cold Harbor light cue sheets; "Turned into D + B", 1983; 147232 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Cold Harbor technical specifications, 1985; 147231 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Cold Harbor Theater Artaud Jan, 1987; 147230 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Cold Harbor costumes Sept, 1985; 147229 (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Cold Harbor sound cue sheets Oct, 1984; 147228 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Cold Harbor packing lists, 1985; 147227 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Cold Harbor sound cue scripts, undated; 147226 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Cold Harbor sound cue sheets, 1984; 147225 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Cold Harbor light notes, cue sheets; The Public Theater, 1985; 147224 (Box 8, Folder 323)
      see also oversize for light plot
    - Cold Harbor hook-ups and rigging; SUNY Purchase, 1984; 147223 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - Cold Harbor lighting; Paris, 1984; 147222 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Cold Harbor tour budgets, intineraries Fall-Spring, 1985-1986; 147221 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - Cold Harbor touring, 1986-1987; 147220 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Iowa City, 1986-1987; 147219 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Missouri Repertory Theatre, Kansas City, MO, 1986-1987; 147218 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Krannert Center, University of Illinois, 1986-1987; 147217 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Humboldt State University, CA, 1986-1987; 147216 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Southwest Missouri State University, 1986-1987; 147215 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Washington University, St. Louis, 1986-1987; 147214 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Cold Harbor tour; UC Davis, 1986-1987; 147213 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - Cold Harbor tour; Theater Artaud, 1986-1987; 147212 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - Cold Harbor notes; Washington, DC, 1988-1989; 147211 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - Cold Harbor contact sheets, schedules; (season includes Prelude to Death in Venice; Dead End Kids; It's a Man's World) Spring, 1987; 147210 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - Cold Harbor Arts Midwest, 1986; 147209 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - Cold Harbor Apple Corps Theater tech, 1987; 147208 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico City, 1989; 147207 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: agreements, per diems, 1989; 147206 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: expense report, 1989; 147205 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: freight, tech, 1989; 147204 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: production, 1989; 147203 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: missing crate, 1989; 147202 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Cold Harbor Mexico: receipts, 1989; 147201 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - Cold Harbor film: budget, accounts, 1989; 147200 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - Cold Harbor film: budget, accounts, receipts, 1989; 147199 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - Cold Harbor tour history, blurbs, misc., 1989-1990; 147198 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - Cold Harbor brochure, undated; 147197 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - Cold Harbor film: notes, financial, etc., 1989; 147196 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - Cold Harbor program copy, 1985; 147195 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - Cold Harbor touring blurbs, 1987; 147194 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Cold Harbor tour expenses, schedules, 1986-1988; 147193 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Cold Harbor Actors' Equity agreements, 1986-1987; 147192 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Cold Harbor Actors' Equity agreements, 1987; 147191 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Cold Harbor correspondence, 1986-7; 147190 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Cold Harbor / A Prelude to Death in Venice public relations, 1987; 147189 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Cold Harbor program, press release; New York Shakespeare Festival [The Public Theater], 1983; 147188 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Cold Harbor film development, 1988-1989; 147187 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Cold Harbor film, NEH correspondence, 1989; 147186 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Cold Harbor NEA interim performance report, 1988; 147185 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Cold Harbor financial, 1987; 147184 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Hajj "stills for film", undated; 147183 (Box 9, Folder 364)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235823
    - Hajj postcard; Japan tour, undated; 147182 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - Hajj tech notes, undated; 147181 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - Hajj project description, undated; 147180 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - Hajj Performing Garage, 1982; 147179 (Box 9, Folder 368)
    - Hajj National Video Festival, 1982; 147178 (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - Hajj The Public Theater, 1983; 147177 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - Hajj CalArts, 1983; 147176 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice Dance Theater Workshop, 1986; 147175 (Box 9, Folder 372)
    - Hajj financial; Los Angeles Theater Center Summer, 1986; 147174 (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice Japan tour, undated; 147173 (Box 9, Folder 374)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice gobo; Japan tour, undated; 147172 (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - Hajj expenses; Museum of the Moving Image, 1989; 147171 (Box 9, Folder 376)
    - Hajj tech, 1988, 1991; 147170 (Box 9, Folder 377)
    - Hajj development letters, 1982-1983; 147169 (Box 9, Folder 378)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice box office records; Dance Theater Workshop, 1986; 147168 (Box 9, Folder 379)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice program copy, undated; 147167 (Box 9, Folder 380)
    - Hajj receipts (video related), 1986; 147166 (Box 9, Folder 381)
    - Hajj video research, 1985-1986; 147165 (Box 9, Folder 382)
    - Hajj correspondence, 1983-1986; 147164 (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - Hajj / A Prelude to Death in Venice promotional; Dance Theater Workshop, 1986; 147163 (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - Hajj sample touring promotional materials, 1983; 147162 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - Hajj Walker Art Center flyers, 1986; 147161 (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice correspondence, budgets, schedules, 1984-1988; 147160 (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice video project, 1986; 147159 (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice J. Kane agreement, 1987; 147158 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice tech notes, undated; 147157 (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice expenses, receipts; Washington University, St. Louis, 1987; 147156 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice contract agreement, 1987-1988; 147155 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice notes, undated; 147154 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice production history, undated; 147153 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice interview with Lee Breuer by Nicoletta Cherubini, undated; 147152 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice contracts, 1986; 147151 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Stephen Peabody, undated; 147150 (Box 9, Folder 397)
      includes head shot
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice blurbs, undated; 147149 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice about, undated; 147148 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice rehearsal party, backstage party May 6, 1986; 147147 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine announcements, 1984, 1986; 147146 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine negatives for poster/program, undated; 147145 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine holograms research, 1984; 147144 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine tech requirements, press, 1984-1987; 147143 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine project description, undated; 147142 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine technical research and inquiries, 1984; 147141 (Box 9, Folder 406)
      includes "National Geographic" Vol. 165, No. 3
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Holographic Film Co. agreement, tech specs, 1981-1986; 147140 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine MIT residency, 1986; 147139 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Performing Garage, 1984; 147138 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Westbeth Theatre, undated; 147137 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine ground plan; Radford Univerisity, VA, 1988; 147136 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Radford University, VA, 1988; 147135 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine development, 1981-1982; 147134 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine tour, 1986; 147133 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine touring inquiries, 1982-1984; 147132 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine budget, 1983-1984, 1988; 147131 (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine attendance, undated; 147130 (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine film and hologram storage, 1984; 147129 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine promo tape info, 1984; 147128 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Imagination Dead Image trunk with holographic film stored with cylinders, 1984; cuid5972; 1 item one trunk with film and cylinders (Item MSS.133.cuid5972)
      Scope and Contents
      Ruth Maleczech
      Works of art.
    - California tour material: maps, guides, hotels, etc., 1986-1987; 147127 (Box 9, Folder 420)
    - Pretty Boy inquiries, 1984-1985; 147126 (Box 10, Folder 421)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235831
    - Pretty Boy press release, 1984; 147125 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Pretty Boy Wooster Group, Inc., The Performing Garage, 1984-1985; 147124 (Box 10, Folder 423)
    - Through the Leaves correspondence with Kroetz and Downey, 1981-1990; 147123 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Through the Leaves tech notes, undated; 147122 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - Through the Leaves sound cue sheets, 1990; 147121 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - Through the Leaves lighting; Public Theater, 1984; 147120 (Box 10, Folder 427)
      see overize for light plot, set design
    - Through the Leaves lighting; Public Theater, 1990; 147119 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - Through the Leaves technical information, 1985-1986; 147118 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - Through the Leaves light plot, hook-up; Israel Festival, 1986; 147117 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - Through the Leaves resumes, undated; 147116 (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - Through the Leaves sound, undated; 147115 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - Through the Leaves production information; Women's Interart, 1983-1984; 147114 (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - Through the Leaves cue sheets; Women's Interart, 1984; 147113 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - Through the Leaves box office records; Women's Interart, 1984; 147112 (Box 10, Folder 435)
      see also oversize for box office spreadsheet
    - Through the Leaves agreement; Women's Interart, 1984; 147111 (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - Through the Leaves light cue sheets and sound hook-ups; Festival de Théâtre des Amériques, Montreal, 1985; 147110 (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - Through the Leaves Festival de Théâtre des Amériques, Montreal, 1985; 147109 (Box 10, Folder 438)
    - Through the Leaves production information; Public Theater, 1984; 147108 (Box 10, Folder 439)
    - Through the Leaves Israel Festival, Jerusalem, 1986; 147107 (Box 10, Folder 440)
    - Through the Leaves / Lear / Company Israel Festival, Jerusalem, 1986-1990; 147106 (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - Through the Leaves Israel Festival, Jerusalem, 1986; 147105 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - Through the Leaves Israel tour intinerary, maps, guides, etc., 1986; 147104 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - Through the Leaves tour budgets, 1986, 1988; 147103 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - Through the Leaves technical information; Public Theater, undated; 147102 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - Through the Leaves box office records; Public Theater, 1984; 147101 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - Through the Leaves financial; Public Theater, 1984; 147100 (Box 10, Folder 447)
    - Through the Leaves comp list with notes, 1990; 147099 (Box 10, Folder 448)
    - Through the Leaves performance report sheets, 1990; 147098 (Box 10, Folder 449)
    - Through the Leaves Public Theater, 1990; 147097 (Box 10, Folder 450)
    - Through the Leaves box office records; Public Theater, 1990; 147096 (Box 10, Folder 451)
    - Through the Leaves press; Public Theater, 1984; 147095 (Box 10, Folder 452)
    - Through the Leaves press, 1985; 147094 (Box 10, Folder 453)
    - Through the Leaves program; Public Theater, 1984; 147093 (Box 10, Folder 454)
    - Through the Leaves flyer and program, 1984, 1990; 147092 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Through the Leaves program copy; Israel Festival, 1986; 147091 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - Through the Leaves correspondence, 1990; 147090 (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - Through the Leaves program; Interart Theatre [March 13-May 6], 1984; 147089 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - Through the Leaves sample touring promotional materials [press], 1984; 147088 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Through the Leaves touring recommendations, 1984-1988; 147087 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Through the Leaves Israel contract, 1986; 147086 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - Through the Leaves contracts and agreements; Public Theater, 1990-1991; 147085 (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Through the Leaves Interart Theatre, 1984, 1990; 147084 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Through the Leaves designer contract, 1984-1986; 147083 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Through the Leaves Actors' Equity agreements, 1985-1990; 147082 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Flow My Tears description, undated; 147081 (Box 11, Folder 466)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235849
    - Flow My Tears rights, 1984-1988; 147080 (Box 11, Folder 467)
    - Flow My Tears Philip K. Dick bio and press, undated; 147079 (Box 11, Folder 468)
    - Flow My Tears New England Foundation for the Arts opening/reception; invitations, comp list June 20, 1985; 147078 (Box 11, Folder 469)
    - Flow My Tears Boston Shakespeare Co; photos, contracts, correspondence, 1985; 147077 (Box 11, Folder 470)
    - Flow My Tears Boston: travel and lodging, 1985; 147076 (Box 11, Folder 471)
    - Flow My Tears ARTS/Boston, ARTS/MAIL, 1985; 147075 (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - Flow My Tears schedule April-June, 1985; 147074 (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - Flow My Tears Boston: advertisements, 1985; 147073 (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - Flow My Tears Boston: press agent correspondence, PR, promo material, 1985; 147072 (Box 11, Folder 475)
    - Flow My Tears Triplex, 1985; 147071 (Box 11, Folder 476)
    - Flow My Tears New York International Festival of the Arts, 1988; 147070 (Box 11, Folder 477)
      includes photograph
    - Flow My Tears New York contracts, 1988; 147069 (Box 11, Folder 478)
    - Flow My Tears NYU Tisch April-Aug, 1988; 147068 (Box 11, Folder 479)
    - Flow My Tears benefit performance June, 1988; 147067 (Box 11, Folder 480)
    - Flow My Tears NYU Tisch: tech packet: construction, lights, sound, etc., undated; 147066 (Box 11, Folder 481)
    - Flow My Tears development, 1985-1986; 147065 (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - Flow My Tears development, 1988; 147064 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Flow My Tears New England Foundation for the Arts grant, 1984-1986; 147063 (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - Flow My Tears New York: budgets Sept, 1985; 147062 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Flow My Tears budgets, 1985-1989; 147061 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - Flow My Tears ticketing, 1987-1988; 147060 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - Flow My Tears Boston box office records, 1985; 147059 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - Flow My Tears press clippings and blurbs, 1985; 147058 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - Flow My Tears correspondence re: article in "New Age Journal" Oct 24, 1985; 147057 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - Flow My Tears Actors' Equity contracts May-June, 1985; 147056 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Flow My Tears tax forms, undated; 147055 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Flow My Tears poster design, 1988; 147054 (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - Flow My Tears program material; biographies, 1985-1988; 147053 (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - Flow My Tears production elements, undated; 147052 (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - Flow My Tears expenses: receipts, 1988; 147051 (Box 11, Folder 496)
    - Flow My Tears expenses: receipts, 1988; 147050 (Box 11, Folder 497)
    - Flow My Tears expenses: payroll sheets, receipts, check requests, 1988; 147049 (Box 11, Folder 498)
    - Flow My Tears expenses: receipts, check requests, etc., 1988; 147048 (Box 11, Folder 499)
    - Flow My Tears miscellaneous notes, undated; 147047 (Box 11, Folder 500)
    - It's a Man's World project descriptions, 1985; 147046 (Box 12, Folder 501)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235856
    - It's a Man's World tour technical specifications, 1985; 147045 (Box 12, Folder 502)
    - It's a Man's World technical specifications, notes, undated; 147044 (Box 12, Folder 503)
    - It's a Man's World design photocopies, undated; 147043 (Box 12, Folder 504)
    - It's a Man's World bios, undated; 147042 (Box 12, Folder 505)
    - It's a Man's World related print material, press, 1986-1987; 147041 (Box 12, Folder 506)
    - It's a Man's World artist contracts, agreements, 1985; 147040 (Box 12, Folder 507)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles press, promo material, 1985; 147039 (Box 12, Folder 508)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles travel and housing, 1985; 147038 (Box 12, Folder 509)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles Theatre Center contract, 1985; 147037 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles Theatre Center: schedule, inventory, correspondence, etc., 1984-1985; 147036 (Box 12, Folder 511)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles Theatre Center press release, 1985; 147035 (Box 12, Folder 512)
    - It's a Man's World Los Angeles celebration Aug-Nov, 1985; 147034 (Box 12, Folder 513)
    - It's a Man's World Apple Corps Theater tech specs, drawings, 1986-1987; 147033 (Box 12, Folder 514)
    - It's a Man's World Apple Corps Theater, 1987; 147032 (Box 12, Folder 515)
    - It's a Man's World postcard/flyer, 1987; 147031 (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - It's a Man's World Apple Corps Theater lighting, 1987; 147030 (Box 12, Folder 517)
    - It's a Man's World artist agreements, 1987; 147029 (Box 12, Folder 518)
    - It's a Man's World Actors' Equity: LATC, Apple Corps, 1985, 1987; 147028 (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - It's a Man's World tech receipts, 1987; 147027 (Box 12, Folder 520)
    - It's a Man's World budgets, 1985-1987; 147026 (Box 12, Folder 521)
    - It's a Man's World fundraising/development, 1986; 147025 (Box 12, Folder 522)
    - It's a Man's World rights, 1985-1987; 147024 (Box 12, Folder 523)
    - It's a Man's World post production notes, 1987; 147023 (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - It's A Man's World ticket stubs, 1987; 152111 (Box 135)
    - Starcock Apple Vail bio, press, 1983-1984; 147022 (Box 12, Folder 525)
    - Starcock summary, undated; 147021 (Box 12, Folder 526)
    - Starcock contact sheets, undated; 147020 (Box 12, Folder 527)
    - Starcock notes Sept 18, 1985; 147019 (Box 12, Folder 528)
    - Starcock schedule Nov-Dec, 1985; 147018 (Box 12, Folder 529)
    - Starcock financial: budgets, invoices, etc., undated; 147017 (Box 12, Folder 530)
    - Starcock benefit Dec 18, 1985; 147016 (Box 12, Folder 531)
    - Starcock artist agreements Oct, 1985; 147015 (Box 12, Folder 532)
    - Starcock biographies/program copy, undated; 147014 (Box 12, Folder 533)
    - Starcock Westbeth Theatre Center agreement, 1985; 147013 (Box 12, Folder 534)
    - Starcock promo art work, undated; 147012 (Box 12, Folder 535)
      includes prints, negative, and slides
    - Starcock press release, promo material, 1985-1986; 147011 (Box 12, Folder 536)
    - Starcock Westbeth Theatre Center house manager info, 1985; 147010 (Box 12, Folder 537)
    - Starcock sound: specs, inventory, cue-sheet, 1985; 147009 (Box 12, Folder 538)
    - Starcock technical specs, 1985, 1989; 147008 (Box 12, Folder 539)
    - Starcock lighting: hook-up, cue sheet Nov-Dec, 1985; 147007 (Box 12, Folder 540)
    - Starcock slide cue sheets, undated; 147006 (Box 12, Folder 541)
    - Starcock box office forms, undated; 147005 (Box 12, Folder 542)
    - Starcock box office daily sheets, ticket stubs Dec 6-Dec 29, 1985; 147004 (Box 12, Folder 543)
    - Starcock box office summaries Dec, 1985; 147003 (Box 12, Folder 544)
    - Company program copy, undated; 147002 (Box 13, Folder 545)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235864
    - Company Public Theater; correspondence, invitations, 1983; 147001 (Box 13, Folder 546)
    - Company University of Massachusetts at Amherst; lighting hook-up, tech notes March, 1985; 147000 (Box 13, Folder 547)
    - Company tour schedule Fall, 1986; 146999 (Box 13, Folder 548)
    - Company press releases, 1982-1983; 146998 (Box 13, Folder 549)
    - Company rights, 1982; 146997 (Box 13, Folder 550)
    - Company rights, Beckett, 1986-1991; 146996 (Box 13, Folder 551)
    - Company tour specs, budget, 1983-1992; 146995 (Box 13, Folder 552)
    - Company technical info, undated; 146994 (Box 13, Folder 553)
    - Company notes: potential Israel tour, 1988; 146993 (Box 13, Folder 554)
    - Company touring inquiries, 1989; 146992 (Box 13, Folder 555)
    - Company letter of agreement, 1991; 146991 (Box 13, Folder 556)
    - Worstward Ho tour specs Oct 1, 1986; 146990 (Box 13, Folder 557)
    - Worstward Ho concept, notes, 1986; 146989 (Box 13, Folder 558)
    - Worstward Ho set notes, undated; 146988 (Box 13, Folder 559)
    - Worstward Ho correspondence, budgets, inventory, etc. Spring, 1986; 146987 (Box 13, Folder 560)
    - Worstward Ho Classic Stage Company rental agreement, 1986; 146986 (Box 13, Folder 561)
    - Worstward Ho Classic Stage Company; contact sheet, schedule, financial, tech, 1986; 146985 (Box 13, Folder 562)
    - Worstward Ho benefit, 1986; 146984 (Box 13, Folder 563)
    - Worstward Ho University of Kansas, 1993; 146983 (Box 13, Folder 564)
    - Worstward Ho inventory for Rio de Janeiro, 1995; 146982 (Box 13, Folder 565)